行动
Let's go.
快点 快点
Come on, come on.
嘿
Hey.
你能别吃这种东西了吗
Can you stop eating those?
怎么了
What?
嗯，会有口臭
Well--they just kind of make your breath--
布莱恩 我正在看电视
Brian, I'm watching this.
噢 只是新闻而已
Come on, it's just the news.
是啊 我正在看
Yeah, well, I'm watching.
真扫兴
Well, that's discouraging.
怎么了
What?
看到你穿这身睡衣的时候我就该知道
I guess I should have known when I saw those pajamas.
这是你的睡衣
They're your pajamas.
没错
Exactly.
这睡衣有什么问题吗
What's wrong with them?
我是说 我们以后都不上床了吗
l mean, are we ever gonna have sex again?
嘿，你想要怎样
Hey, what do you want?
我们不常见面
We never see each other,
见到面的时候 时间也不早了
and when we do, it's late,
我们不怎么谈心 又很少出去约会
and we haven't talked,and we don't go out,
所以在你（招妓）之前
so why don't you
就不能至少假装你还喜欢我吗
at least try acting like you like me before you--
我爱你 你知道的
I love you.You know that.
我知道 布莱恩
I know, Brian.
你知道吗 我真的很累了
You know what? I'm just really tired.
我们跟安德鲁・所罗门进行现场连线
We're going to take you live now to Andrew Solomon,
他在金斯堡为我们做警方突击执法的现场报道
who's in Wilkinsburg, where a police raid is in progress.
安德鲁
Andrew?
你好 朱莉
Thank you, Julie.
没错 我现在正站在
That's right, I'm standing here at the corner
多佛和宾夕法尼亚大道的街角
of Dover and Penn avenue,where a bust has
警方对一家
just occurred at an oriental massage parlor
涉嫌进行卖淫活动的按摩院
where allegedly, a lot more than just massages
进行突击执法
could be purchased.
现在观众朋友们可以看到
Now as you can see here,the police are in the
警方逮捕了几名犯罪嫌疑人
process of making several arrests.
现场的一名警官
One of the officers here...
私聊室
莫娜
明科夫→我想你
伊格内修斯赖利→进入theloveiorn.com
我
Oh...
的
My...
天
God.
这个特别的场所
This particular establishment...
妈咪
Mommy?
没事儿的 艾蜜莉
It's OK, Emily.
别害怕 宝贝儿
Don't be scared, OK, honey?
跟着这个好心的阿姨
Just go with this nice lady,
我一会儿就回来接你 好吗
and I'll come see you in a couple hours, OK?
好了 丫头 勇敢点儿 好吗
All right. Be my brave girl, honey, OK?
阿尔文
Alvin!
阿尔文 他们把我女儿带走了
Alvin, they're taking my daughter!
阿尔文 他们带走了艾蜜莉
Alvin, they took Emily.
我的脑海一片混乱
there is trouble in my mind
法外情真 第二季 第五集
有黑暗
There is dark
有黑暗，也有光明
There's dark,and there is light
主演：西蒙 贝克
无法无天
There is no order
一片混沌，充满罪恶
But there is chaos and there is crime
今夜无人归家
There is no one home tonight
在我脑海里的帝国
In the empire of my mind
编剧：大卫 霍兰德
对不起 扰你清梦了
Sorry to get you out of bed.
没关系
It's Ok.
我本想让安东尼・翰莱姆来处理这事儿的
I wanted Anthony Hanram to handle this,
但是我联系不上他
but I couldn't track him down.
你能想象一个辩护律师还整天只带个传呼机
You'd think a defense attorney would carry a pager--
没关系 阿尔文 没事儿
That's OK, Alvin, it's all right.
呃
Uh,
抱歉没法保释你
sorry about the bail.
咱们现在手头没那么多现钱
We--we just don't have that kind of money in the house.
明天一早我就能把钱凑齐
So, uh, I'll get it for you first thing tomorrow morning.
露露
Lulu...
露露 能看着我吗
Lulu, could you look at me?
明天 你到援助中心
Tomorrow, at the clinic,
分配一下比较急的案子
distribute the cases that are pressing and
让其他人照常工作
get continuances for the others.
好 在你回来之前我会帮忙的
Right. I'll cover for you until you get back.
还需要你帮个忙
I need something else.
当然
Sure.
麻烦你去一趟书记员办公室
I need you to go to the clerk's office
查一下有没有一个女人
and find out if bail has been set
叫亚尼内・克拉内的保释记录
for a woman named Janine Crane.
她是谁
Who is she?
她是和我一起
She's a woman who, uh...
被逮捕的那个女人
the woman I was with when I got arrested.
嘿 杰克
Hey, Jake.
嘿
Hey.
你听说马斯特森的事儿了吗
So did you hear about Masterson?
我听说地区检察官接了一个极简单的案子
Yeah. I hear the D.A's got an open-and-shut case.
他们抓了个左撇子的女人
They caught the woman left handed.
得了吧
Come on.
你看 他雇了翰莱姆帮他辩护
Well, look, he hired Hanram to defend himself.
这回 他又有个好帮手
Once again, he's in good hands.
这回真的是相当严重
It's a pretty--pretty serious matter.
明摆着 这女人会说自己是清白的
Apparently, the woman claims she's innocent.
但我相当肯定她一定有事儿
I'm pretty certain she had a hand in it.
杰克 我们昨天开了合伙人会议
So, Jake, we had a partner's meeting yesterday
讨论了一下你的事儿
to discuss your deal.
好
Great.
所以你现在是授薪合伙人了（区别于收益分红合伙人）
So you are an income partner.
虽然没有投票权
You--you don't have a vote yet,
但你的薪水
but your salary is as we agreed,
是我们之前说好的奖金
and your bonus will be
会视你表现而定
commensurate to your performance.
好的 要优先处理的案子是哪个
OK. So what's the first order of business?
赫斯勒・科林尼斯
Hessler Kleaners.
在他们觉得出售特许经营权之前
Before they commit to franchising,
我们需要做一个法律层面的可行性分析
we need a legal feasibility study,
法人组织文件
incorporation documents,
还有一份授予特许经营权的协议范本
and a master franchise agreement
周四上午之前要完成
by Thursday morning.
没问题
Done.
祝贺你 杰克
Congratulations, Jake.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
对阿尔文的事儿感到很遗憾
Yeah, and it's, uh, it's a shame about Alvin.
嗯
Yeah.
希望这件事能尽快了结
Sure hope he gets off.
哈洛韦尔先生
Mr. Hallowell?
叫我塞思
Oh--Seth.
塞思 好的
Seth. OK.
这件事对于援助中心来说事关重大
Well, this is a very serious problem for the clinic.
我们董事会成员
All of us on the board,
都很关注
we're all very, very concerned.
我会尽我所能帮忙处理的
Well, just let me know what I can do to help.
目前 暂时工作接手援助中心
For now, take over the clinic.
代表援助中心
Be the face of the place.
暂时不要提阿尔文
Now, make no mention of Alvin.
我们会尽可能把公众关注的焦点
We're going to do our best
从阿尔文身上移开
to spin this away from Alvin
转而投射向你
and onto you.
什么
Excuse me?
你的形象正是我们现在需要的
Your image is what we need right now.
像你这样 已婚又有强烈家庭观念的人
Someone like you, married with family values,
来应付媒体
to meet with the press,
我的意思是 帮助我们渡过难关
I mean, to help us through this time.
阿尔文只是被起诉
Alvin has just been charged,
还没有被定罪
he's not convicted of anything.
他的合同里写明了违反功德行为条款
Moral turpitude clause, it's in his contract.
你的合同里也有
It's in yours, as well.
这里是主要处理家庭法律事务的援助中心 路易斯
I mean, this is a family clinic, Louise--
别 我明白 我理解 我只是说
Oh, no, I know, I understand that, I'm just saying--
我们雇你是作为这个中心的副主任
You were hired as associate director of this clinic.
现在是该你履行职责的时候了
It's time for you to do that job.
露露 嘿
-Lulu. -Hey.
阿尔文的事儿
So, this whole Alvin thing's
有点过了哈
a little crazy, huh?
如果你问我的话 我认为很愚蠢
I think it's stupid, if you ask me.
真的 为什么
Really? Why?
当然了 竟然去按摩院
Yeah, going to a massage parlor?
你对去按摩院的男人有意见吗
You have a problem with a man going to a massage parlor?
我对凌晨三点起床去保释阿尔文有意见
I have a problem with getting up at 3 a.m. to bail Alvin out,
我对因为他不能控制自己
and I have a problem taking on all of his cases
而要我接受他的工作有意见
because he can't control himself.
好吧
Yeah.
我这去我办公室了
Well, I'll--I'll be in my office.
尼克 十点半有个庇护听证要你去
Uh, Nick, you have a shelter hearing at 10:30.
布赖恩特・威尔科克斯
Bryant Wilcox.
好
OK.
芭芭拉
Barbara!
很抱歉打扰你
I'm sorry to bother you.
别 没的事儿
No, no, it's no problem, I--
我只是最近手头
I just, uh, I've got a lot of work
事儿有点多 所以
going on right now, so--
那改天吧
Maybe later.
什么事儿
Well, what is it?
我能
Can I just--
请你帮我个忙
please, uh, I need some help,
这个事儿我没法跟援助中心的人开口
and I can't talk to anybody at L.S.P. about it.
到我办公室吧
OK, why don't you come on in my office?
你电脑开着吗
Is your computer on?
开着 怎么了
Yeah, why?
能上网吗
Uh, can you go on the internet?
链接到“相思”这个网站
Punch in "thelovelorn."
怎么了
Why?
点开看看
Just punch it in.
是开玩笑还是怎么的
Is this some kind of joke?
连上了吗 嗯
-Got it? -Yeah.
好 滑到网页最下面
OK, scroll down to the bottom.
你这张照片拍的不错
That's a good picture of you.
点击
Click it.
看看这个胖蠢货，她要跟我做爱呢
芭芭拉 我很抱歉
Barbara, l'm sorry.
天呐 太过分了
Gosh, that sucks.
我常上钢城单身网
Yeah, I used to go to this site, iron city singles,
（匹兹堡在十九世纪初因冶炼行业发达而被称为钢铁城）
我没有电脑 所以会在办公室待到很晚
I'd stay late at work 'cause I don't have a computer.
总之就是我遇到一个男的
Anyway, I met this guy there.
网名是lgnatiusjreilly
lgnatiusjreilly,
出自《笨伯联盟》这本书 书挺不错的
you know,from "Confederacy Of Dunces," which is a great book,
这是另一回事儿了
but another story.
我的网名是莫娜明科夫 我们开始在网上聊天
I was myrnaminkoff, and we started chatting,
我不知道
and, I don't know,
那种有人可以谈谈
there was something about it,
就只是聊天
having someone to talk to, just talk,
见不到面 也不用互相评头论足
without being judged or stared at.
我只是觉得
I just felt like,
这么长时间以来
for the first time in a very, very long time,
第一次有人真正听我倾诉
someone was really listening to me,
关心我
considering me.
你还是坐下
Why don't you, uh--
这种情况持续了多长时间
how--how long did this go on for?
几个月
A few months.
我们开始聊天
We started chatting.
聊过几次之后他要我的照片
He asked for my picture after a couple of chats,
然后我说我不会给的
and I said that I wouldn't give it to him
因为我之前经历过
because l've had experiences with men
类似的情况
when they see me.
我也不想让他看到我真实的样子
And I didn't want him to imagine me like I am, I guess.
然后有一天 我给他发了邮件
And then at one point I emailed him.
跟他说了我的体型
I told him about my size.
他说没关系
He said that it was fine,
他自己也不完美
that, uh, he wasn't perfect, either.
后来我从我妈那里找来了照片
So I had my mom take that picture,
在办公室扫描后发给了他
and I scanned it at work, and then I sent it.
昨晚他发邮件给我让我
And then last night he emailed me to go
去相思网站看一下
to the lovelorn site.
我很遗憾 芭芭拉
I'm so sorry, Barbara.
我想把照片撤下来 杰克
I want it down, Jake.
我不会责怪你
Yeah, well I don't blame you,
但是 这很难办
but, uh, listen, this is a tough case.
我们可以主张诽谤
I mean, we can argue defamation,
但是他也有他的权利
but he's got his rights.
我只想把照片撤下来
I want it down.
别管我 放开我
Leave me alone!Leave me alone!
过来 布赖恩特 过来吧
Come on, Bryant, come on out.
噢
Damn!
斯洛特小姐 这孩子的律师在哪儿
Miss Solt, where is this child's counsel?
我来了 法官大人
I'm here, your honor.
他现在已经不受控制了 法林先生
He is out of control, Mr. Fallin.
马上让他安静 不然我就当庭处罚
Calm him down or you're sanctioned!
过来 过来
Hey, come here, come here.
哦
Ow! Ow!
放开我
Let go of me!
放开我 放我下来 你给我过来
-Let go of me! Put me down! -Come here, you.
好了 听着
All right, listen.
马上给我站好 不许吵闹
You're going to stand here and you're going to be quiet, OK?
到底怎么回事儿
What is going on?
他现在怎么了
What is he doing now?
他正在抽搐
He's having a convulsion.
詹姆斯 抱歉
James, excuse me, we have 3 families
又有上三个新案子进来
coming in with new cases.
你能接一下吗
Will you take them?
我已经忙得不可开交了
I'm swamped.
大家都一样
We all are.
这些
Those...
大家好
Hey, everybody.
露露 跟赛思谈过之后 我要跟你谈一下
Lulu, after I meet with Seth, I need to see you.
社服部 抱歉让您久等了
Social Services, sorry to keep you waiting.
天呐 阿尔文 我们都很担心你
Gosh, Alvin, um, we've been concerned.
援助中心会扛过去的
The clinic is going to get through this.
关于你
Well, about you.
赛思 这事儿会了结的
Seth, this will all clear up.
我现在面临的只是三等轻罪的指控
I'm facing a third degree misdemeanor
而且案子并不一定站得住脚
and they have a weak case.
听着 阿尔文
Listen, Alvin,
是你一手创办了这个地方
you built this place.
你成就了这里 这是从你的角度出发
You made it what it is. It's your vision.
你要我退出吗
You want me out of here?
阿尔文 不是我
Alvin, it's not me.
你的合同里包含道德条款
Your contract contains a morals clause.
董事会决定在事情了结前让你暂时停职
The board wants to suspend you until this is resolved.
我是董事会成员 是我组织了董事会
I'm on the board. Hell, I created the board.
要是我没被定罪
If I'm not convicted of a crime,
董事会还会说我的不是吗
how can the board argue that I did anything wrong?
你在一家按摩院被警察抓了
You were arrested in a massage parlor.
阿尔文 你的确做错事了
Alvin, you did something wrong.
不 赛思 我没错
No, Seth, I didn't.
露露 嗯？
Lulu. -Yeah.
我需要你代理吉妮・克兰
I need you to represent Janine Crane.
为什么
Why?
社服部带走了她的女儿艾蜜莉
Social services took her daughter Emily.
他们把她安置在庇护所
They put her in a shelter and they're
他们还说暂时不能让她离开
making noises about not letting her out.
你知道 阿尔文 哈洛韦尔先生说
Ugh. Alvin, you know, Mr. Hallowell said that--
这不是赛思的法援中心 是我的
This isn't Seth's clinic, it's mine.
听着 她已经是我们的客户了
Listen, she's already a client.
五年前 我代理了吉妮的庇护听证
5 years ago, I represented Janine in a shelter hearing.
你不觉得这是利益冲突吗
You don't think this is a conflict?
我已经跟她讨论过这个问题了
I've already discussed this with her.
她已经声明放弃了可能存在的利益冲突
She's waived whatever conflict there might be.
另外 我已经被暂时停职了
Besides, for now, I'm suspended.
这孩子急病突发
He had a seizure.
已经有人带他去匹兹堡市立医院了
They took him to Pittsburgh County.
他母亲呢
Where's the mother?
还在服刑 她四周前因为毒品犯罪入狱
In prison--she was arrested for drugs 4 weeks ago.
还没有父亲的下落
The father's not in the picture.
在他母亲被捕之前他住在哪儿
Where's he been staying since the mother's arrest?
过去几个月他一直跟他的阿姨谢丽尔
He's been staying with his aunt Cheryl for the
住在一起
past couple of months.
她接他一起住是因为
She took him in because the mother
他母亲一旦嗨起来就几周不回家
would be gone for weeks at a time getting high,
但这个阿姨基本管不了他
but the aunt can't handle him.
这就是我们今天开庭的原因
That's why we were in court today.
孩子的母亲有做医疗决定的行为能力吗
Can the mother make medical decisions for the child?
她还在吸毒的恢复期
She's finding recovery challenging.
就在上周 身体还被检出毒品
Just last week, they found drugs in her cell.
法林先生 我现在指定你为医疗行为监护人
Mr. Fallin, I need to appoint a medical guardian.
你觉得你能承担这个责任吗
You think you can handle the responsibility?
我
Well, I...
威尔科克斯女士说
Ms. Wilcox said her sister Cheryl
她的妹妹可以做医疗决定
could make medical decisions.
那法林先生你就作为临时的医疗监护人
Oh, Mr. Fallin will step in as temporary medical guardian.
我让书记员再通知你新的听证时间
I'll have my clerk notify you of the new hearing date.
鉴于这孩子的情况 庭上陈述尽量简单明了
Be prepared to fully brief the court on the child's condition.
事情很简单 吉妮
It's pretty simple, Janine.
你赢了官司 就能继续养育你女儿
You win your case, you'll probably keep your daughter.
否则 她就要继续待在收养机构
Otherwise, she will end up in foster care.
我认为你是想养育艾蜜莉的
I'm assuming that you want to keep Emily.
当然
Of course.
好的
All right.
他们会检查你的居住条件
Well, they're going to look into your housing situation,
还有什么是我需要知道的吗
so is there anything that l need to know?
关于
About?
你住的地方
Where you live.
我的公寓
Um, in an apartment.
就在按摩院上面
Above my business.
你是说你就住在那什么楼上
Oh, you mean you live right above the--
对
Yeah.
怎么了
What?
你为什么做这一行
Why do you do this?
为什么 对
-Why? -Yeah.
为了钱 还能为什么
Money. Why else?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不是为了钱工作 所以
I mean, I don't work just for money, so...
那很好
Well, good for you.
你什么意思
What does that mean?
没上大学
No college.
也没上高中 真的 没父母 没钱
No high school, really. No parents, no money.
我并不是想给你讲一个悲惨的故事
You know, I'm not trying to tell you a sob story,
但是看看你
but looking at you, I--I'm guessing
我猜一定有人很爱你
somebody out there loves you,
帮你
helps you.
但是 我是说 出卖肉体
But, still, I mean, selling, uh--
你的很多客人都是已婚人士
a lot of the men that you see are--are married.
那不是我的错
That's not my fault.
那他们的妻子呢
What about their wives?
我也不能说这是她们的错 这
I can't say it's their fault, either.It's...
有些男人就是这样
the way some men are.
就只是性而已 奥尔森夫人
It's just sex, Mrs. Olsen.
没什么意思
It's not fun.
我也不喜欢 但这是我谋生的手段
I don't like it, but it's something I know how to do.
妈妈
Mommy!
艾蜜莉 我好想你 我想你
Emily, oh I missed you. I missed you.
现在还不能让她走
They can't release her.
为什么
Why not?
吉妮还没有被定罪
I mean, Janine hasn't been convicted of anything yet.
开庭之后是什么情况我们还不清楚
We don't know what's going to happen with the court case,
艾蜜莉眼下还是要待在庇护所
so for now, Emily has to stay in the shelter.
我找沃瑟曼医生
Dr. Wasserman l'm looking for.
沃瑟曼医生 我是尼克・法林
Dr. Wasserman, I'm Nick Fallin.
布赖恩特・威尔科克斯 对吗 你是他的医疗监护人
Bryant Wilcox, right? You're his medical guardian?
对
That's right.
他的片子显示没有动脉瘤
His films show no aneurisms,
也没有脑瘤 他不是癫痫发作
no brain tumors, he's not an epileptic,
并没有什么明显病变
nothing normally associated
造成他之前的抽搐
with the type of seizure that he suffered,
但他的血液化研究结果显示
but the results from his blood work
血铅量是85
show a lead level of 85.
很高吗
Is that high?
高于10就已经很危险了
Anything above 10 is considered dangerous.
那他这样的原因是
Well, uh, how could it get like that?
关于含铅涂料的法案
The projects are full of lead paint
早在几年前就作废了
that should have been abated years ago.
孩子误食墙皮
The kids eat the paint chips,
或是吸入墙面的灰尘和碎屑
inhale dust that flakes from the wall.
当父母意识到的时候 孩子病已经很重了
By the time the parents realize it, their child's already sick.
这能造成他的抽搐吗
Could it have caused his seizure?
他的抽搐 是一种强烈的机能亢进
His seizure, his intense hyperactivity,
他的言语功能和生长发育迟缓
his speech and developmental delay,
还有神经系统损伤
and neurological damage.
能治吗
Can it be treated?
螯合治疗能尽可能的减少
Chelation therapy attempts to drain the
血液中的铅含量
lead particles from the blood.
但是病人会很痛苦 而且疗效有限
It's painful, and only so effective.
嗨
Hi.
还记得我吗 在法庭上 我叫尼克
Remember me from court? My name's Nick.
布莱恩特喜欢拥抱
Bryant likes to hug.
我需要他医疗记录的副本
I need a copy of his records.
我要把他的接受治疗的记录搜集完整
I'm trying to put together a medical history.
我们也一样
So are we, but we don't even know
但我们现在还不知道他有没有自己的小儿科医生
if he has a pediatrician,
也联系不到他母亲
and we can't locate the mother.
我们还想让你帮忙联络到他母亲
We were hoping you'd know where she is.
好的
Sure.
私聊室
莫娜
明科夫→伊格内修斯赖利，在吗？
伊格内修斯赖利→嗯？
莫娜明科夫→我要你撤销我的照片和邮件
莫娜
明科夫→我会付你三百美元
伊格内修斯赖利→一千
莫娜明科夫→五百
伊格
内修斯赖利→九百
莫娜明科夫→六百
伊格内修斯赖利→要现金，
九点
钟在奥克兰的快乐汤姆餐馆外，我去找你
你能告诉我你儿子的小儿科医生的名字吗
Can you tell me the name of your son's pediatrician?
一个诊所
Some clinic.
就在福布斯和奥克兰大街那儿
The one up on Forbes and Oakland.
我带布莱恩特去那儿看病
Took Bryant there.
我能跟你妹妹谢丽尔联系吗
Well, should I just ask your sister Cheryl?
问布莱恩特的事儿吗
About Bryant?
她没带他看过医生
She never took him to no doctor.
你们母子不住一起的时候也是你带他去的
You took him even when he wasn't living with you?
他是我的孩子
He's my kid.
那你还记得给布莱恩特看病
Do you remember the name of any of the doctors
的医生的名字吗
that treated Bryant?
你需要的话 就去问我的律师
You need anything like that, you talk to my lawyer.
你的公设辩护人怎么会有
Why would your public defender
你儿子的医疗记录呢
have a medical record on your son?
不是他 是我的私人律师
Not him, my private guy.
汉森先生 马克・汉森
-Mr. Hansen. -Marc Hansen?
好吧 谢谢
Oh, OK. Thank you.
我和汉森先生 我们正准备起诉房东
And me and Mr. Hansen-- we're suing the landlord
因为含铅超标的涂料
on account of the lead paint.
我出去的话 就能把布莱恩特带回来 对吧
When I get out, I get Bryant back, right?
这要由法庭决定
That's for the court to decide.
布赖恩特・威尔科克斯 当然
Bryant Wilcox? Sure.
铅中毒 卡特街的项目
Lead case. Carter Street projects.
有好多生病的孩子 你怎么知道他
A lot of sick kids. How do you know him?
我是他的代理人
I'm representing him.
她妈妈在监狱 我要安置他
His mom's in jail, and I'm placing him.
监狱
Jail?
听到这个消息真是好 对吧
Nice to let her lawyer know, huh?
但这就是接人身伤害案子
But that's the kind of clients
经常要应付的客户
you deal with when you do personal injury.
生意怎么样 挺好
-How's business, man? -It's fine.
你真是到处跑啊
You've been all over the place.
我两周前打电话到你的新律所
I tried calling you two weeks ago at the new firm,
但是电话被转接到你老爸那儿
but the phones forwarded me back to your Dad's place.
我们又在一起工作了
Well, we're working together again.
现在律所叫法林&法林
It's called Fallin and Fallin.
在我替布莱恩特找到安置家庭之前
So before I can find Bryant a home,
我需要他的医疗记录
I need a copy of his medical records.
这孩子需要被安置到
Is there a chance this kid might
集体家庭之类的地方吗
need to be placed in some kind of group home?
能够提供特殊服务的家庭 没错
Special needs home, yeah.
这对你的案子有帮助 索赔能得更多钱
That helps your case. Worth more money.
塔拉 帮我把布莱恩特・威尔科克斯的资料复印一份
Tara, could you please make a copy of the Bryant Wilcox file?
朱莉怎么样 美丽依旧
-How's Julie? -Beautiful as ever.
带我向他问好
Say hello to her for me.
周六晚上
Hey, why don't you come over for dinner
到我家吃饭吧
Saturday night, huh, you know?
好久没见了 她也挺想见你的
It's been too long. I know she'd love to see you.
好 没问题 我很乐意过去
Yeah, it'd be great. I'd like to do that.
我今晚就让塔拉把布莱恩特的医疗记录
All right, I'll have Tara messenger
传给你
a copy of Bryant's meds to you tonight.
好
All right.
能发到法律援助中心吗
Can you--can you send them to legal services?
你还要在那儿干多久
How much longer you got to do that?
我只是过来看看吉妮
I just came by to see how things
和艾蜜莉的事儿怎么样了
are going with Janine and Emily.
艾蜜莉现在暂时由社服部的人照看
Uh, well, Social Services is keeping Emily for now.
不能把她弄出来吗
You can't get her out?
劳里・斯洛特不同意
No. Laurie Solt said no, so...
阿尔文
Alvin...
你真要为了这个丢掉工作吗
are you really going to lose your job over this?
地区检察官给我提了变诉交易
The D.A' s offering me a deal.
只要我把吉妮供出来
I give up Janine, and they reduce
他们就起诉我轻罪
my charge to a violation.
那很好
Great.
就这么做吧
Well, do it.
他们让我撒谎
Well, they're asking me to lie.
吉妮和我之间 从来就不是金钱交易
Janine and I--it was never about money.
我没付过钱给她
I never paid her.
阿尔文 你知道 你这么努力工作
Alvin, you know, you work so hard and--
大家都很敬重你
and everyone respects you,
我不明白 为什么
I don't understand. I mean, why?
你为什么去
Why would you go--
这跟别人有什么关系
What's one got to do with the other?
就因为我的性生活 我就不是一个合格的律师了吗
Am I any less of a lawyer because I have a sex life?
当然不是 但我说的是妓女
No, but--but the prostitute is what I'm talking about.
她是妓女 但跟我在一起时不是
She may have been a prostitute, but she wasn't with me.
lgnatiusjreilly
lgnatiusjreilly?
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
我是杰克・斯塔卡
I'm Jake Straka.
这是勒令停止通知函（对涉嫌欺诈的人士寄发的法律文件）
And this is a cease and desist letter.
什么
What?
Myrnaminkoff希望你关闭自己的网页
Myrnaminkoff wants off your web site.
我希望今晚午夜之前撤掉你发布的照片
I expect it to be down by midnight tonight.
你是在网上跟我约到这儿的人吗
You're the one that told me to come here?
对 没错
Yeah, that's right.
我的钱呢
Where's my money?
你拿不到 傻蛋
You don't get it, dumb ass.
要是你不把照片撤掉
lf you don't take this down,
我就把你和你父母告到破产
I'm going to sue the crap out of you and your parents, OK?
是吗 对
-Oh, really? -Yeah.
我的钱呢
Where's my money?
你能得到的只有一场关系 兄弟
All you're getting is a lawsuit, pal.
伙计们
Fellas!
这货耍我们
This guy posed as a fat chick.
兄弟 这只是个法律纠纷好吗
Look, guys, this is a legal dispute, OK?
我才不管是什么
I don't care what it is.
别激动
Hey, take it easy.
他就是那个说要给我们600块的人
He's the one that promised us 600 bucks.
别激动 好吗
Hey, take it easy, OK? Just take it--
我就要钱
Hey, I want my money.
好吗
OK?
把这个吃了
Eat this.
芭芭拉
Barbara.
我跟Ignatiusjreilly见面了
I met with Ignatiusjreilly.
他不同意撤掉照片
So he's not gonna take the pictures down.
嗯
OK.
咱们直接起诉他
So we're gonna go after him in court.
真要这么做
We are?
我马上向法院提交针对他的特别禁令
I'm gonna hit him with a petition
今天就传唤她到庭
for special injunction, haul him into court today.
基于什么理由 诽谤
-On what basis? -Defamation.
但是你说 不 那个网页上说
-Yeah, but you said -No, the site states
你想跟他上床
that you wanted to have sex with him.
并配着你的照片 这就是诽谤
That goes to your character. That is defamation.
首先 我们要他关闭网页
So, first we're gonna get him to take the site down,
然后我们正式起诉他
then we're gonna sue him.
要是他没有可用于执行赔偿的存款 就执行他的其他财产
If he doesn't have any money, we go after his assets.
要是他没有
If he doesn't have any assets,
就要求执行他父母的财产
we go after his parents' assets.
他父母
His parents?
我去了市里 我也认识人
Yeah, I went to Pitt, too, and I know people.
我要让他被学校开除
So I'm getting him thrown out.
他还是大学生
He's a college student?
很抱歉 他是
Yeah, I'm sorry, he is.
我要好好收拾他
I'm gonna bury his ass.
我以后到你的信息就马上赶来了
I came as soon as I got your message.
病情更严重
Uh, this seizure was worse.
他现在是昏迷状态
He's in a coma.
他会醒过来的 对吧
But he's gonna come out of it, right?
现在还很难说
It's too early to know.
我拿到了他的医疗记录
I have a copy of his medical records.
上面显示上个月他的血铅量持续上升
They say that his lead levels kept increasing
之后有所下降
up until the last month and then leveled off.
下降代表
Well, if they leveled off,
他离开了铅污染环境
that means the exposure probably ended.
需要决定是否继续生命维持系统的时候
If a decision needs to be made about life support--
不 我
No. I--
什么
No, what?
不 我
Just no. I--
阿尔文 进来吧
Alvin, come on in.
听着
Listen--
阿尔文 你不需要
Alvin, you don't have--
吉妮和我有性关系
Janine and I have an adult relationship.
很显然
Clearly.
我的意思是
What I mean is,
几年前 我刚离婚 当时我是她的代理人
years ago, after I got divorced, I represented her.
我们相处了一段时间 互相喜欢
We spent time. We liked each other.
你为什么跟我说这些
Why are you telling me this?
我从没付钱给她 劳里
I never paid her, Laurie.
她不是那种
She was not--is not-- the kind of person
那种大家以为的
who deserves to be known just as another--
那种什么
Another what?
妓女
A prostitute.
那她算什么
Then what is she?
她是个好女人
She's a kind woman.
一个好妈妈
A good mother.
她理应跟她的女儿在一起
She deserves to have her child--with her.
要是她进监狱了呢
And if she goes to prison?
那是另外一回事儿了
Well, then that's another story.
在犯罪指控决定之前
But until the criminal charges are resolved,
为什么不让她们娘俩
why not allow her to have the time
待在一起呢
she should have with her daughter?
好
OK.
谢谢
Thank you.
埃尔文 嗯
-Alvin? -Yeah?
就算你给她钱了又怎么样
If you paid for it, so what?
辛西娅・威尔科克斯 对
-Cynthia Wilcox? -Yeah?
我是尼克・法林 我们之前通过电话
Hi, I'm Nick Fallin. We spoke earlier.
他怎么样
How is he?
你的公寓做过墙体涂料含铅量测试吗
Um, have you ever had your apartment tested for lead paint?
卫生部门有人来过
The Department of Health came through.
他们有什么发现吗
And what did they find?
她们跟我说没事儿
Told me it was clean.
好 在布莱恩特跟你在一起的时候
OK. In the time that Bryant was with you,
你有主要到他行为上的
did you ever notice
一些变化吗
any kind of change in his behavior?
他退步了
He was just going backwards.
已经学会的东西也忘记了
Forgetting stuff he already knew.
连衣服也不能自己穿了
Boy couldn't even dress himself anymore.
我手上有布莱恩特的验血报告
I have the records of Bryant's blood tests
检查的时间一直持续到你姐姐被捕
the weeks leading up to your sister's arrest.
是你带他去验血的吗
Did you take him for those tests?
不 都是米里亚姆带他去
No. Myriam did all that.
就算她在外面嗑嗨了
Even when she was out binging,
但是每次她都会回来
she'd always make sure she'd come by
带布莱恩特去诊所
to take Bryant to the clinic.
她确实有她的问题 但她是个好妈妈
She's got her problems, but she's a good mother.
好 谢谢
Great. Thank you.
艾米 给我复印一份网络侵犯隐私权的案例
Amy, I need a copy of the cases on internet privacy law, OK?
杰克 我看了一下你整理的
Jake, look, I took a look at these Kessler Kleaner papers
凯斯勒・科林纳尔的资料
that you prepared. Um--
好
OK.
我没法拿给我爸
I can't give them to my father.
很差吗
They're bad?
不太好
Well, they're not great.
好 我会按时搞定的
OK, I'll have them done on time.
你在忙什么
What are you working on?
芭芭拉・鲁辛斯基来找我
Uh, Barbara Ludzinski came by to see me.
她和网上的某个人又点问题
She--she got into this relationship with this guy on the net,
这个人羞辱她
and he humiliated her, so I'm just trying
我在想办法让这人把网页关闭
to get him to take the site down.
赫斯勒的案子你需要帮手吗
Do you need a hand with that Hessler case?
不 不 我很快就好
No, no. I'm on top of it.
我可以接过来 不
-I could take it over. -No.
需要我帮忙处理鲁辛斯基的事儿吗
Do you want me to help with the Ludzinski problem?
不 这是我自己的事
No. This is my thing.
那好吧
All right.
艾米 我需要判例的复印件
Amy! Damn it, I need a copy of the case law, OK?
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你帮忙让艾蜜莉回来
For getting them to give Emily back to me.
你得知道这可能只是暂时的
You know that might only be temporary?
一旦你被定罪 我知道
-If you're convicted -I know...
我有麻烦了
I'm in trouble.
地区检察官
The D.A.--
他们向那个新来的女孩儿李施压 要她作证
they're pressuring that new girl, Lee, to testify.
他们也在向我施加压力
They're pressuring me, too.
我从没要过你的钱
But I never asked you for money.
没人会相信的
Nobody wants to believe that.
他们让李说什么她都会说的
Look, Lee's gonna say whatever they want her to say.
她才19 很害怕
She's 19. She's scared.
吉妮 她会把我们两个都供出来的
Janine, she could implicate both of us.
你要接受交易
You're gonna take a deal?
我明白我俩的关系并不是
I know our relationship wasn't like
他们希望我说的那样
they want me to say it was,
但我知道你是做哪一行的
but I also know how you make your living,
有没有我的证言
and they're gonna get you for that--
他们都会给你定罪的
with or without my help.
亨利・利恩将鲁辛斯基小姐的
Henry Lean posted Miss Ludzinski's
私人通信记录和照片
personal correspondence and photograph
发布在网上 并附上这样的标题
on a website under a heading which read,
“这个死胖子想跟我上床”
"Check out this fat loser who wants to get it on with me."
这是在暗示鲁辛斯基小姐
Now, this insinuates that Miss Ludzinski
自愿与陌生人发生性关系
is willing to have sex with a complete stranger,
依据习惯法 已经构成诽谤
and is therefore, under common law, defamation, per se.
此话怎讲
How so?
自18世纪起公开声称一女子是
Well, a claim that a woman is unchaste is defamatory
不贞洁的便构成法律意义上的诽谤
as a matter of law, and has been since the 1700s.
法官大人
Judge...Ahem.
我不是律师 但正在读法律预科
I'm not a lawyer, but I am pre-law.
我们都知道宪法第一修正案的涵义
We have covered what the First Amendment means.
所以我知道 一旦鲁辛斯基小姐
So, I know that as soon as Miss Ludzinski
自愿把照片给我
gave me that material,
我就有权按照我自己的意愿加以使用
I was allowed to do whatever I wanted with it.
我问过我的法律老师
Now, I asked my law professor,
他跟我说
and he told me that, uh, she--
鲁辛斯基小姐没有
"Miss Ludzinski has no reasonable
保护其隐私的期待可能性
"expectation of privacy.
目前的判例已经明确证实了这一点
"It's been well established by the courts already."
这是他说的原话
I mean, that's what he told me.
杰克
Jake?
杰克 你已经尽力了
Jake, you did your best.
尽力了
My best?
我刚刚竟然被一个刚进大学的毛头小子收拾了
Just got my ass handed me on a platter by a college student?
你跟那个小（混蛋）
-Well, uh -did you ever ask that little--
你跟那个小
Did you ever ask that little--
你是否跟他说过不要把照片
Did you ever ask him to not show the letters
和通信记录给别人看
or the photos to anyone?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
好好想想 妈的 到底跟他说过没有
Think, damn it. Did you ever ask him?
可能吧
I may have.
还有我看过的通信记录吗
Is there any correspondence that I haven't seen?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
我要申请他的电脑作为证据
I'm gonna subpoena his computer.
听这 杰克 现在回办公室
-Listen, Jake -Look, just go back to work.
检查一下所有保存的东西
Check everything that you ever saved.
看一下有没有你要求他不要把照片拿给别人看的记录
See if you ever asked him not to show the letters to anyone.
我觉得可能找不到
Well, I don't think I did.
去找 我们就能以违反约定起诉
Do it! We can claim breach of contract.
但是 杰克 就这么做 好吧
-But, Jake -Look, just do it, OK?
我会再找你
I'll come by later.
我知道你一直在喂布莱恩特吃墙皮
I know you've been feeding Bryant paint chips.
我不明白你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
这就能解释为什么布莱恩特的血铅量
Then explain to me why Bryant's lead levels
在你被监禁前的那段时间仍然持续上升
kept increasing the month before your incarceration.
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
那个该死公寓到处都是铅
There was lead all over that damn apartment.
最后一个月他并没有在你的公寓住
He wasn't living in your apartment that last month.
他跟你妹妹住在一起
He was living with your sister,
而她的公寓的铅污染检测是正常的
and her apartment is lead-free.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你一周接布莱恩特一次
You would pick Bryant up once a week,
把他带到你们的公寓 然后喂他墙皮
and take him to your apartment and feed him paint chips.
几小时之后 你再开车带他去诊所
A few hours later, you would take a drive to the clinic,
验血
and he would get a blood test.
你疯了
You're crazy!
我要去告诉地区检察官
I'm gonna go and talk to the D.A.
他没说这会引发癫痫
He didn't say nothing about no seizures.
谁 那个律师
-Who? -The lawyer.
汉森
Hansen?
我带布莱恩特去做学前体检的时候
When I took Bryant to the doctor for his start of school check-up,
他们说他铅中毒
they said he had the lead.
跟我住一栋公寓的朋友说
So one of my friends in the building
我应该去找汉森
said l should go see Mr. Hansen,
说他能帮我要些赔偿
that he could get us some money.
但是汉森先生却说
But Mr. Hansen said that--
我儿子的血铅量还不够高
that my boy's level was too low to be worth his time.
要是我能做点什么
But I could do stuff that could
就能拿到近百万的赔偿
make the case worth a million dollars.
他跟你这么说的
He told you that?
对
Yeah.
他跟所有的母亲都是这么说的
He told all the mothers that.
嘿
Hey.
你在这干嘛
What are you doing here?
就 忙个案子
Just--just working on a case.
你呢
You?
偷闲
Snuck in.
在大家都下班之后
After everybody was gone.
不想一个人坐在家里
Didn't feel like sitting around my apartment.
我这周想了你的事
I thought about you this week.
在监狱的那晚
That night in jail.
我之前也待过监狱
I've been there before, you know.
因为抗议被捕
Getting arrested for protests.
但是
But, uh,
如果是因为一些私人的问题进去 那感觉
when you're in for something personal, it's--
很害怕 对
-Scary. -Yeah.
你在等待庭审的时候
When you were awaiting trial,
他们给你提了变诉交易 对吗
they offered you a deal, right?
但是没有接受 对
-But you didn't take it? -No.
为什么
Why not?
我什么都没做错
I didn't do anything wrong.
嘿 哦 谢谢
-Hey. -Hi. Oh, thank you.
怎么样
So?
我找不到
I can't find anything.
网上的你全都查过了吗
You looked everywhere on the site?
我没跟他说过不能让别人看
Well, I--I never told him he couldn't show anyone else.
你确定你都查过了吗
You sure you looked?
硬盘呢
What about your hard drive? Did you--
杰克 拜托
Jake, please.
我不想再找了 好吗
Um, I--I don't wanna look at this stuff anymore, OK?
我的意思是
I mean--
那就撒谎 不行
-Lie. -No.
你只要说 没准儿哪会有
No, just say that maybe you have it on--
杰克 不 你看 芭芭拉 我
-Jake, no. -Look, Barbara, I--
我知道你是好意
I know you mean well.
过去这几天
And these last couple of days,
我从来都不知道你能对我
I never imagined that you would feel so strongly...
芭芭拉
Barbara--
这么好
about me.
你放下了手边的一切
That--that--that you could-- could drop everything
这么热心帮我
and be so, I don't know, passionate?
他们 他们打了我
They--they beat me up.
我去见他的时候
When I went to see them, they, uh--the kid
那孩子和他朋友
and his friends-- they--
把我打了 按倒在大街上
They--they punched me and they threw me on the ground, OK?
我现在是一家律所的合伙人
I--I am a partner in a law firm now.
他们竟然那么做
And they--they did that.
所以我现在要求你做的事
So what--what I am asking you to do is--
只是为了让你自己心理平衡 对吗
Let you get even, right?
为了让你心理平衡
Let you get even.
对不起
Sorry.
不 是我误解了
No, I--I just misunderstood.
就这么算了吧 杰克 好吗
Let it go, Jake, OK?
如果我可以做到 你也行 就这么算了吧
If I can, so should you. Just--just let it go.
老兄 请坐
Hey, man. Have a seat.
拿到我发给你的文件了吗
Get those files I sent you?
嗯
Yeah.
周六晚上
Saturday night
朱莉有个从费城来的朋友
Julie has a friend coming in from Philly. Huh.
长得很漂亮
A very pretty friend.
是你跟你的客户说
Did you tell your clients
让她们喂自己的孩子吃墙皮的吗
to feed their children paint chips?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
米里亚姆・威尔科克斯
Myriam Wilcox.
她跟我说如果她儿子的血铅量不够高
She told me you wouldn't take her case
你就不接她的案子
until her son's lead levels were higher.
她的情况不够起诉 但我我没跟她说
Her case wasn't worth enough, but I didn't tell her--
她说你跟那栋公寓的所有母亲都这么说了
She said you told that to all the mothers in the building.
好吧
Yeah, well...
记得你是在跟谁说话 尼克 好吗
Let's remember who you're talking with here, Nick,All right?
一个正在服刑的瘾君子
This is a crack addict in prison.
得了吧
Come on.
你难道没有发现很奇怪吗
You didn't find it strange that the kid's levels
她第二次来找你的时候那孩子的血铅量足足高了四倍
were 4 times higher on the second visit to your office?
我有37件这样的案子 尼克
I have 37 lead cases, Nick.
我又不是医生
I'm not a doctor, OK?
不负责注意这些数值
I don't monitor them all.
但你确实跟她说血铅量高
But you did tell her the case would be worth more
就能拿到更多的赔偿
with higher lead levels.
我们为什么谈这个兄弟
Why are we even having this conversation, man?
这女人蠢到喂自己的
I mean, if this woman is stupid enough
孩子吃墙皮
to feed her kid lead paint, huh?
她要是这么傻
If she's that dumb,
我跟她说过的任何事都会被误解
anything I say to her could be misconstrued.
误解
Misconstrued?
或者说她只是遵循你的建议
Or was she just following instructions?
我什么都没做错
I didn't do anything wrong.
尼克 你要是走漏了小子 你的客户
Nick, if you make any noise about this, your client,
我的客户 一个大子儿都见不到了
my client, won't see a dime.
这是你希望的吗
Is that what you want?
我跟地区检察官说过了
I spoke to the D.A.
只要你指证汉森
Testify against Hansen
他们就不告你虐待儿童
and you won't be prosecuted for child abuse.
我不知道
I--I--I don't know.
他们的目标不是你 是汉森
They don't care about you, they care about Hansen.
所以你要我告发我们那栋公寓里的母亲
And so I gotta--I gotta snitch on all the moms in my project?
对
Yes.
给她们自己孩子喂铅的那些人
The ones giving their kids the lead?
对
Yes.
好吧
OK.
还有一件事
There's one more thing.
这是啥
What's this?
这是你自愿放弃亲权的文件
It's your consent to relinquish parental rights.
什么意思
What's that mean?
意思是从法律意义上讲
It means that you will no longer
你再也不是布莱恩特的母亲了
have legal standing as Bryant's mother.
你要把我的宝贝从我身边带走
You wanna take my baby away from me?
你要对我的孩子这么做
You gonna do that to my boy?
你知道没有母亲在他身边
You know what it's gonna be like for him,
他未来的成长会是什么样吗
growing up without a mother?
知道
Yeah.
别再对我不敬 绝对不要
Do not disrespect me! Ever!
嘿
Hey.
你穿这件睡衣看起来很漂亮
You look very pretty in these pajamas.
要是脱掉就更漂亮了
But you look a lot better out of them, huh?
布莱恩
Brian--Brian.
你到底怎么了 露露
What the hell's wrong with you, Lulu?
我们这一周都挺好的
I mean, I've been nice all week,
一起出去吃了晚餐
and, we, uh, went out to dinner.
一周三次打电话
And I called you at the office
到你办公室跟你说我爱你
at least 3 times a day to tell you I love you.
你还要我怎么做
I mean, what else do I have to do?
别再跟妓女胡搞
Stop having sex with hookers.
你说什么啊
What are you talking about?
你心里清楚
You know what l'm talking about.
我们结婚的几周前
A few weeks before we got married,
你在酒店买春
you got arrested for solicitation
被便衣警察抓了现行
by an undercover cop in the bar of the grand hotel.
你提出不做申辩请求 罚款六百
You pled no contest got a $600 fine
连续四周周六下去在圣约翰学校强制教育
and 4 Saturday afternoons at John School.
根本不是你所说的在哥伦布的额外课程 是圣约翰学校
Not extra classes in Columbus-John school.
露露 你是不是觉得我很蠢
-Lulu -Do you think I'm stupid?
看在上帝的份儿上 我当过书记员
I was a clerk, for God's sakes.
法院系统都有我的朋友
I've got friends all over the court system.
尼克跟你说的
Nick told you?
不是 但我知道是他代理你
No, but I know he represented you.
露露 听我说
Lulu, listen--
我只是不知道
You know, I just don't know how
你怎么能跟别的女人做那种事
you could do that with other women.
跟妓女
Hookers.
然后回到家面对我
And then come home to me.
不是你
It's not you.
你他妈说对了 当然不是我
You're damn right it's not me!
是你
It's you!
我承认我做了蠢事
It was a stupid thing I did.
只是婚前压力大
Like last-second jitters.
好吧
Oh, OK.
那你只有这一次吗
So then you only did this once?
对
Yes.
别对我撒谎 我中邪了
-Don't lie to me. -I mean I'm sick.
这是一种病态 我需要帮助
It's a sickness. I need help.
闭嘴 你才不是病
Shut up! You're not sick!
但是 布莱恩 为什么
But, Brian, why-- I mean, what are you--
你在外边到底想寻求点什么
what are you looking for out there?
你到底要什么
Really, what the hell are you looking for?
要我离开吗
Should I leave?
不需要
No.
我接受了变诉协议
I accepted a deal.
很抱歉听到这些
I'm sorry to hear that.
两年 十二个月就能出狱了
Two years--I'll be out in 12 months.
我会安置好艾蜜莉的
I'll make sure Emily gets a good placement.
就算不是李
If it wasn't Lee, it would have been
也会是我的其他员工
one of my other employees
或者是某个他们抓到的客人
or one of the customers that were busted.
我不会作证指认你的
I wouldn't have testified against you.
为什么
Why not?
因为
Because...
因为我没付你钱
Because you don't pay me money.
阿尔文 几年前
Alvin, a few years ago
孩子的事儿你帮了我
you helped me out with my kid.
每次有法律上的麻烦 我就打电话给你
Every time I had a legal problem, I called you.
没错
Right.
阿尔文
Alvin,
这就是你付钱的方式
That's how you paid me.
B・卢廷斯基：多谢你帮忙
J・斯特拉卡：不客气，芭芭拉，一会儿去喝一杯怎样
杰克 文件我看过了
Jake, I took a look at that work.
很好
It's very good.
我整晚没睡赶工
I--I stayed up all night working on it.
当时很有状态
I was kind of, like, in the zone.
那很值得
Well, it was worth it.
赫斯勒会很满意的
Hessler's gonna like it a lot.
我知道
I know.
芭芭拉・鲁辛斯基的事儿怎么样了
What happened with Barbara Ludzinski--that thing?
那个熊孩子
Uh, the kid. I...
我把他搞定了
I dealt with him.
很好
Good.
进来
Come on in.
他们撤回了起诉
They dropped the charges.
他们的目标是吉妮 所以这事儿过去了
All they wanted was Janine, so it's behind us.
我还有活儿要忙
Well, I got a lot of work to do.
阿尔文 我们很高兴 真的很高兴
Alvin, we're pleased. We're very pleased.
这样继续保留你援助中心主任的职位
And we have no qualms in you retaining your position
我们就没有什么疑虑了
as director of the clinic.
谢谢
Thank you.
但你还是被董事会除名了
However, your seat on the board has been reassigned.
没有定罪啊
There was no conviction.
我们还是觉得不太合适
We're not comfortable.
是我一手组建了这个援助中心
I founded this clinic.
但是你得向董事会负责
Right, but you report to the board.
规章明确要求主任必须是
The bylaws require that a director of the clinic
董事会成员
be on the board.
这次的情况 副董事必须这么做
In this case, the associate director will have to do.
什么
What?
奥尔森被指定替代你在董事会的职位
Mrs. Olsen has been appointed in your place.
所以 你还是援助中心的主任
So, you'll still be director of this clinic,
但是露露有参与董事会决议投票的权利
but Lulu will have the vote upstairs.
我很抱歉 阿尔文 但我们得考虑捐助者们的想法
I'm sorry, Alvin, but we have donors to think about.
法林先生
Mr. Fallin.
嗨 我刚刚
Oh, I--hi. I just--
探病时间已经过了
visiting hours are--
我知道 工作忙一时走不开
Yeah, I know. I got held up at work.
没关系 不用着急
That's fine. Take your time.
反正你是唯一来看他的人
You're the only one to come visit him, anyway.
法外情真贴吧
感谢
人人影视
翻译：费伦泽
制作：Michael Song
感谢收看 下集再见